clicksnm.com 2015-04-21

# ClickSNM : Privacy Policy

**Our privacy policy** **Important - Please read carefully**

Our Privacy Policy is intended to give you useful information about the way we collect and use personal information and how we use cookies. Clicksnm.com is one of the trusted coupon websites. We will not gather any personal data from you unless you particularly provide it, and we will only utilize that info for the purposes to which you have accepted. We will maintain a record of your name, age, details with the purpose of sending information on deals, promo codes,coupon codes or coupons, and newsletters. Our site will never provide your personal details to other companies for marketing purposes. See this website for more data. ClickSNM may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from July 2013.

**By using our website you accept the terms of this Privacy Policy:** **The personal information we collect about you:**

When you make purchases from clicksnm.com online stores we may collect the following personal data about you:

  * Name
  * Postal address(Not mandatory)
  * Telephone and fax number 
  * Email address

We will not sell your personal information to any third party sites.

**What do we do with the information we collect?**

We use the information we collect in a number of ways:

  * Internal record keeping
  * We may utilize the information to improve business services
  * We occasionally send promotional emails about new offers and deals or other discount information to your email ids.
  * Sometimes we may also use your information to reach you for market research purposes. We may approach you by email or phone.

Electronic Newsletters and Site Notification

As a coupon site, we are constantly changing the website design or add new features or offers. Therefore, as a service we provide our registered members or email ids , electronic newsletters and new site (or site update) notifications to keep our users updated. Newsletters and website notifications can be subscribed to at any time by accessing our Signup Section, located on the ClickSnM homepage.

Consumers may remove themselves from any mailing list by following the instructions contained at the end of every newsletter or website notification email. 

**Operational Information**

You can buy items from our online merchant sites, in future we may ask you to register an account with us. In this process, we will require you to provide your name, email address, a password, your billing information and delivery address. Once accepted by the customer the following demographic information will be used by us for email campaigning, newsletters, promotional deal articles.

**Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. However, as no security measures are perfect or impenetrable, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us.

**The Privacy Policy also gives information about cookies:** **How we use cookies**

A text string of information is stored in your computer Hard disk. The purpose of the cookie is when you visit the website next time it will remember who you are. When the website is accessed, a secured encrypted session cookie is sent by us for validating your access. This temporary cookie allows you to visit various sections of the website and therefore helping us to understand which pages you find useful and which you do not. The traffic log cookies that are provided by Google help us to identify and analyze which web pages are accessed more by the esteemed customers, thus helping us to improve the quality of our website. Cookies are small amount of information which is sorted on computer hard disk. The website deploys cookies for particular and limited purposes. It is widely used for easier browsing on the website and to make login easier. Our system will copy cookies when you log on to the sites. Cookies allow web applications which can modify its operations to your needs. 

**Links to other websites:-**

We provide links to other websites for coupon code or promo code information that include websites related to ClickSNM through common ownership. These sites may operate independently from www.clicksnm.com, and may not be under our control. These sites may have their own privacy Notices/Policies in place, which we strongly suggest you review if you visit any linked website. We may not be responsible for the content of these sites, any products or services that may be offered through these sites, or the privacy practices of these sites.

We are not responsible for the data collection practices of any sites linked to ClickSNM nor do our linking to third party websites or services constitute sponsorship or endorsement of the content or business practices on these sites. By use of this Site, you have agreed that you will use the hyperlinks to third party sites at your own risk.

**Your preference of association with us:-** **Social Media Platforms**

Communication, engagement and actions taken through external social media platforms that this website and its owners participate on being custom to the terms and conditions as well as the privacy policies held with each social media platform respectively.

This website may use social sharing buttons which help share web content directly from web pages to the social media platform in question. Users are advised before using such social sharing buttons that they do so at their own discretion and note that the social media platform may track and save your request to share a web page respectively through your social media platform account.

You can manage the controls of sharing the information on social networks. While authorizing, you can set privacy options as per your requirement. You can associate with us through the websites like:-

**Children's Privacy:-**

Our other linked sites may contain adult based materials. Parental control is advised to restrict children from using these sites. Children under eighteen years are strictly PROHIBITED. If you use these sites, then it represents that you are at least eighteen years old. ClickSnM is not responsible for any Risks Associated.  
**This site is totally intended for coupons, promo and coupon codes.**

**Information to the Residents of Countries outside USA:-**

ClickSNM has its roots in Atlanta, Georgia. Your Personal Information may be accessed by us or transferred to us in the United States or to our affiliates, business partners, merchants, or service providers elsewhere in the world. By providing us with Personal Information, you consent to such access and transfers; you also acknowledge and agree that Personal Information may be subject to access requests from governments, courts, law enforcement officials, and national security authorities in the United States in accordance with United States laws. We will protect the privacy and security of Personal Information according to our Privacy Statement, regardless of where it is processed or stored.

**Our Contact Information:-**

You may wish to contact us from time to time by sending us emails or by filling in contact forms on one of our websites. We will only utilize this information to respond to your query or suggestion. For customer service or technical questions, please complete the 'Contact Us' form. For questions regarding this Privacy Policy please write to us @[ **info@clicksnm.com**](mailto:info@clicksnm.com)
